

Marlou F. Pepito

Software Engineer

A highly motivated and skilled software engineer with 7 years of experience in designing, developing, and maintaining software applications. Proficient in various programming languages and technologies, with a strong background in web development, mobile app development, data science.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology (BSIT)

Central Philippines State University June 2016 - July 2020

Work Experience

Koda Kollectiv

06/05/2022 - 03/26/2024 Software Engineer Mandaue City Cebu

EmpireOne

04/01/2024 - Current Web Developer San Carlos City Negros Occidental

API's

Google Script API
Google Mail SMTP API
Real Time API (Pusher JS)
Stripe Payment API
SMS Notification API
Google Map API
Twilio API

Skills

- React JS
- React Native
- React Redux
- Flutter
- MySQL
- Laravel
- Tailwind CSS
- HTML
- Bootstrap

Tools

- Chat GPT
- Jira
- Trello
- ClickUp
- Microsoft Word
- Excel
- Power Point
- VS Code